export const Questions = [
  {
    prompt:
      "Who was the king that got overthrown by Robert Baratheon prior to Season 1?",
    optionA: "Tywin Lannister",
    optionB: "Aerys II Targaryen",
    optionC: "Rhaegar Targaryen",
    optionD: "Brandon Stark",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Who on the small council is the best spymaster in all of Westeros, known as the Spider?",
    optionA: "Littlefinger",
    optionB: "Lord Varys",
    optionC: "Tywin Lannister",
    optionD: "Tyrion Lannister",
    answer: "B",
  },

  {
    prompt:
      "This knight of the kingsguard was dismissed by Joffrey and later sought out Daenerys Targaryen in order to join her cause",
    optionA: "Ser Barristan Selmy",
    optionB: "Ser Jorah Mormont",
    optionC: "Dario Naharis",
    optionD: "Tyrion Lannister",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "This army of eunuchs became the prime fighting force for Daenerys Targaryen",
    optionA: "Dothraki",
    optionB: "Second Sons",
    optionC: "Immortals",
    optionD: "Unsullied",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Who did Jon Snow have to kill in 1v1 combat in order to convince the Wildlings to take him to Mance Rayder?",
    optionA: "Lord Of Bones",
    optionB: "Craster",
    optionC: "Qhorin Halfhand",
    optionD: "Alliser Throne",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "This sect of wildlings were known to be fierce cannibals",
    optionA: "Thenns",
    optionB: "Giants",
    optionC: "Raiders",
    optionD: "Wargs",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Who was the commander of the city watch that was removed by Tyrion, replaced by Bronn, and sent to The Wall?",
    optionA: "Littlefinger",
    optionB: "Varys",
    optionC: "Podrick Payne",
    optionD: "Janos Slynt",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who was the real culprit behind poisoning Joffrey?",
    optionA: "Tyrion Lannister",
    optionB: "Cersei Lannister",
    optionC: "Olenna Tyrell",
    optionD: "Margaery Tyrell",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "How was Roose Bolton killed?",
    optionA: "Poisoned by his enemies",
    optionB: "Stabbed by Ramsey",
    optionC: "Hung by smalljon",
    optionD: "Stabbed by Theon",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "What was the name of the mercenary group from Essos hired by Cersei to defend against Daenerys Targaryen?",
    optionA: "Golden Company",
    optionB: "Second Sons",
    optionC: "The Faceless Men",
    optionD: "The Iron Fleet",
    answer: "A",
  },
];
